the name's
McCree it's an honor Fighting by your
side ma'am you always wear a
charmer Brave of you to show your face
around here Jesse well I know how much
you missed me still have a picture of me
at The Hideout I hear on the dart board
bet you look at it every day flattering
really
real nice bike you got Ash what you do
with it Jesse parked it somewhere well
damned if I remember where I left the
keys
though H how about we let bygones be
bygones a you know that's not the way it
works Jesse I was hoping you'd make an
exception for Old Time
sake and how's Bob he's just fine thank
you for your
concern still remember your old house
kind of miss that old sofa it was a
Shay's Lounge it was a
footrest you always were the ambitious
one Ash you make that sound like a bad
thing you'd still be on a farm if it
weren't for me some days it doesn't
sound so
bad you know you never were my type Ash
too competent too
rich believe me I I get wanting to wear
the armor and all but following the old
man around must be nothing but trouble I
don't see it that way to me it's an
honor Diva just tell me one thing
where'd you learn to shoot like that 16
bit
hero you know McCree The Winning Side
would pay much better maybe by yourself
some real clothes my clothes have you
seen some of the things Talon wear
they wouldn't even have to pay me to put
you away then how would you afford the
hospital
bills you might be fast Genji but you
ain't faster than a bullet why don't we
find
out Genji how did you ever get used to
you know it was hard enough for me and
it was just the one arm it was a long
and a difficult road but now I feel at
ease in my own body
why have you come back to this place
McRee the only thing it ever is
unfinished business and unhappy
history you know that sake is not half
bad but I prefer a little bite to my
lior how predictable such an
unsophisticated
taste I heard there's a nice reward for
bringing you fellas in maybe we could
work something out mate
hey McCree do you know what time it is
well I'd say it's about no I see what
you're doing
there you know smoking's bad for your
health well I have faith you can get me
patched back up
doc always thought hiring you was a
mistake the best mistake one could ever
make our courageous
cowboy the years haven't changed you
much have they Jesse well they certainly
haven't changed my feelings about
working with
you Jesse McCree Outlaw reward $60
million the reward could make up for ify
grant money hey come on
now McCree where did you learn to shoot
like that was it Jack Gabriel always was
a good shot but I got a few points poers
from the
best that'd be your
mother just remember far we ain't
playing with toy guns anymore good I'm
much better with the real
thing what's your Halloween costume
going to be this year far
cold I taught you everything you know
not
everything I didn't teach you all my
tricks lucky for me I still have a few
tricks of my
own you look
ridiculous looked in the mirror
lately you weren't giving those guns to
toss them around like trash I don't take
lessons from
you I heard there's a nice reward for
bringing you fellas in try
me I bet you're a big fan of those
old-fashioned cowboy movies aren't you I
thought I was
until I met
you pleasure working with you McCree if
that is your real name don't know what
you heard but my name's not Joel best
remember
that McCree what happened to your arm
always admired yours figured I'd get one
of my
own someone had to do it seems fitting
it'd be me
you needed
killing thought I saw a
ghost don't like shooting a lady but for
you I'll make an
exception long
overdue not fast
enough always was the better
shot didn't have to be this
way Elementary my dear
Winston just like old times
pretty handy with that bow